{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943210197","data":{"timestamp":" 946943210197"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_H_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943217678","data":{"timestamp":" 946943217678"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_H_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943227868","data":{"timestamp":" 946943227868"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_H_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943234461","data":{"timestamp":" 946943234461"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_Y_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943241068","data":{"timestamp":" 946943241068"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943247677","data":{"timestamp":" 946943247677"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_E_K"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943254284","data":{"timestamp":" 946943254284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_G_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943261775","data":{"timestamp":" 946943261775"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_G_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943268466","data":{"timestamp":" 946943268465"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_S_E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943275124","data":{"timestamp":" 946943275124"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_R_E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943281785","data":{"timestamp":" 946943281785"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_G_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943288410","data":{"timestamp":" 946943288410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943295032","data":{"timestamp":" 946943295031"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943308187","data":{"timestamp":" 946943308187"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 35890f40-fd8b-4756-9d90-e95adbfe323d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943329322","data":{"timestamp":" 946943329322"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_H_CH"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943335953","data":{"timestamp":" 946943335953"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_Y_B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943342592","data":{"timestamp":" 946943342592"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943350009","data":{"timestamp":" 946943350009"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_N_E_G"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943356661","data":{"timestamp":" 946943356660"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_E_K"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943363353","data":{"timestamp":" 946943363352"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_G_E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943370001","data":{"timestamp":" 946943370001"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_S_E"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943376691","data":{"timestamp":" 946943376690"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_R_E"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943383346","data":{"timestamp":" 946943383344"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_G_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943389980","data":{"timestamp":" 946943389980"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_E_O_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943396653","data":{"timestamp":" 946943396649"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:E..E.all.10.rand.say.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943409722","data":{"timestamp":" 946943409722"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" be452cf1-9c71-41a5-8b94-c0e8077d735c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_E..E.all.10.rand.say.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_L_H_E"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943455417","data":{"timestamp":" 946943455417"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" moto_maji-kabla-rangi-moto"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" moto"," userResponse":" moto"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943474894","data":{"timestamp":" 946943474893"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_hata-usiku-baada-mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" baada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943477565","data":{"timestamp":" 946943477565"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_hata-usiku-baada-mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" mti"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943480239","data":{"timestamp":" 946943480239"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" usiku_hata-usiku-baada-mti"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" usiku"," userResponse":" usiku"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943499297","data":{"timestamp":" 946943499297"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nta_nta-kishindo-ngozi-zetu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nta"," userResponse":" zetu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943501982","data":{"timestamp":" 946943501982"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nta_nta-kishindo-ngozi-zetu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nta"," userResponse":" ngozi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943504654","data":{"timestamp":" 946943504654"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nta_nta-kishindo-ngozi-zetu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nta"," userResponse":" kishindo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943507314","data":{"timestamp":" 946943507314"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nta_nta-kishindo-ngozi-zetu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" nta"," userResponse":" nta"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943529376","data":{"timestamp":" 946943529376"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchana_uko-kishindo-mchana-mwerevu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mchana"," userResponse":" mwerevu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943537051","data":{"timestamp":" 946943537051"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchana_uko-kishindo-mchana-mwerevu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mchana"," userResponse":" kishindo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943539763","data":{"timestamp":" 946943539763"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mchana_uko-kishindo-mchana-mwerevu"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mchana"," userResponse":" mchana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943576575","data":{"timestamp":" 946943576575"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali_peke-kali-samahani-mungu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943608917","data":{"timestamp":" 946943608917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_kuku-ndege-macho-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943613544","data":{"timestamp":" 946943613544"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ndege_kuku-ndege-macho-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ndege"," userResponse":" ndege"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943633818","data":{"timestamp":" 946943633816"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ndege_kuku-ndege-macho-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943633946","data":{"timestamp":" 946943633946"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 5afc08d2-0074-4ed6-b851-3d8c3cacc11a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_31"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua lilipochomoza asubuhi akapeperuka akiimba kwa ____________."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ____________"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943644947","data":{"timestamp":" 946943644947"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" d7bec715-5406-4e5d-bfd6-6b6ba0f6c10e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943648169","data":{"timestamp":" 946943648168"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" d7bec715-5406-4e5d-bfd6-6b6ba0f6c10e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943659417","data":{"timestamp":" 946943659417"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v8"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943661971","data":{"timestamp":" 946943661970"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943663047","data":{"timestamp":" 946943663046"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943663811","data":{"timestamp":" 946943663810"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943665264","data":{"timestamp":" 946943665264"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943665961","data":{"timestamp":" 946943665961"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_6v3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943670388","data":{"timestamp":" 946943670388"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943670407","data":{"timestamp":" 946943670407"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943670891","data":{"timestamp":" 946943670891"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943671252","data":{"timestamp":" 946943671252"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943672126","data":{"timestamp":" 946943672126"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943672882","data":{"timestamp":" 946943672882"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943673512","data":{"timestamp":" 946943673512"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943677225","data":{"timestamp":" 946943677225"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943678585","data":{"timestamp":" 946943678585"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943678930","data":{"timestamp":" 946943678930"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943679568","data":{"timestamp":" 946943679568"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943681534","data":{"timestamp":" 946943681534"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943681795","data":{"timestamp":" 946943681795"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943682038","data":{"timestamp":" 946943682038"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943682284","data":{"timestamp":" 946943682284"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943685398","data":{"timestamp":" 946943685398"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943686196","data":{"timestamp":" 946943686196"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943686532","data":{"timestamp":" 946943686532"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943686768","data":{"timestamp":" 946943686768"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943688892","data":{"timestamp":" 946943688892"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943689161","data":{"timestamp":" 946943689161"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943689439","data":{"timestamp":" 946943689439"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943689674","data":{"timestamp":" 946943689674"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943689918","data":{"timestamp":" 946943689917"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943690153","data":{"timestamp":" 946943690152"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943690371","data":{"timestamp":" 946943690371"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943691530","data":{"timestamp":" 946943691530"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943704230","data":{"timestamp":" 946943704230"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" dbeb4711-e8bd-4d36-9a9a-354660f62a2a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ND_1v2"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943735819","data":{"timestamp":" 946943735819"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" ca9423be-ab58-4b5f-b527-b948c9724567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943747878","data":{"timestamp":" 946943747878"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" ca9423be-ab58-4b5f-b527-b948c9724567"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943792388","data":{"timestamp":" 946943792388"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 76bb1d09-2b2e-4bd5-9313-80aeebb578dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" pamoja_kubwa-tena-pamoja-kubwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" pamoja"," userResponse":" pamoja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943837053","data":{"timestamp":" 946943837053"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 76bb1d09-2b2e-4bd5-9313-80aeebb578dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kucha_njema-tambarare-kuuliza-kucha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kucha"," userResponse":" kucha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943842589","data":{"timestamp":" 946943842588"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 76bb1d09-2b2e-4bd5-9313-80aeebb578dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kucha_njema-tambarare-kuuliza-kucha"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943842666","data":{"timestamp":" 946943842666"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 76bb1d09-2b2e-4bd5-9313-80aeebb578dc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_34"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Asubuhi Sungura alitaka kujua siri ya Jimbi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943854683","data":{"timestamp":" 946943854683"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943855719","data":{"timestamp":" 946943855719"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943858938","data":{"timestamp":" 946943858937"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943859999","data":{"timestamp":" 946943859999"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943862605","data":{"timestamp":" 946943862604"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943863641","data":{"timestamp":" 946943863641"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943866326","data":{"timestamp":" 946943866326"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943867370","data":{"timestamp":" 946943867369"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943871536","data":{"timestamp":" 946943871535"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943872605","data":{"timestamp":" 946943872605"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943875545","data":{"timestamp":" 946943875545"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943876611","data":{"timestamp":" 946943876611"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943876716","data":{"timestamp":" 946943876716"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943876805","data":{"timestamp":" 946943876805"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 293b6499-ac4c-40a3-a36f-3c8739d65e61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943887792","data":{"timestamp":" 946943887792"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943893630","data":{"timestamp":" 946943893630"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943899905","data":{"timestamp":" 946943899905"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943906410","data":{"timestamp":" 946943906410"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943914177","data":{"timestamp":" 946943914177"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943920918","data":{"timestamp":" 946943920918"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943927321","data":{"timestamp":" 946943927321"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943932403","data":{"timestamp":" 946943932403"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943936364","data":{"timestamp":" 946943936364"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946943942999","data":{"timestamp":" 946943942999"," userId":" 6116002581"," sessionId":" 6116002581_20000104_024620"," gameId":" 6022ef9c-7b5e-470c-9e30-4fa8953c2c40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}